<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
<title type="text">Zoey's World</title>
<generator uri="https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll">Jekyll</generator>
<link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://zoeyrae.com/feed.xml" />
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://zoeyrae.com" />
<updated>2018-10-20T01:32:25+00:00</updated>
<id>http://zoeyrae.com/</id>
<author>
  <name>Zoey Cluff</name>
  <uri>http://zoeyrae.com/</uri>
  <email>zoey.cluff@gmail.com</email>
</author>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soylent Introduction]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://zoeyrae.com/soylent/soylent-introduction/" />
  <id>http://zoeyrae.com/soylent/soylent-introduction</id>
  <published>2015-11-16T00:02:29+00:00</published>
  <updated>2015-11-16T00:02:29+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Zoey Cluff</name>
    <uri>http://zoeyrae.com</uri>
    <email>zoey.cluff@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;I will be the FIRST person to admit I eat like utter garbage. My diet is simply put ramen and Mtn. Dew (and a lot of it). I eat takeaway 2-3 times a week, and it puts a serious damper in my budget. Basically, My poor body gets most of its calories from soda and my frou-frou coffee drinks (Mochas - three shots espresso, steamed milk, chocolate sauce). My exercise is also pretty much non existant. I&amp;#39;m lazyness redefined when it comes to myself. So I&amp;#39;m going to change that (or try to anyway). I&amp;#39;m going to try Soylent for 30 days. I&amp;#39;m kind of a picky eater although recently I&amp;#39;ve branched out to new things, so hopefully this won&amp;#39;t be an instant repulsion thing. Either you like soylent or you hate it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://zoeyrae.com/30dos/soylentemail.png&quot; alt=&quot;Soylent Purchase Email&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m going to blog about it here for 30 days. I ordered enough for 14 days (eating two meals a day), and if things work out like I hope (do they ever?) I&amp;#39;ll order another 14 days worth. Hell, this may turn into a forever (except special occasions) type deal. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;What I hope for:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feel less like garbage. I&amp;#39;ve noticed that the way I eat dramatically influences my anxiety and depression. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get enough calories from food. Not from my liquid intake. This will help immensely no matter if I eat soylent, or actually cook proper meals. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weigh t loss. Nothing dramatic, but I&amp;#39;m gaining weight because my body is always in starvation mode because a packet of ramen and a 2L of soda a day does not make a balanced diet. I&amp;#39;m also going to ramp up my exercise and that&amp;#39;ll help too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This experiment starts next week (The week of Nov. 22 (also my birthday week... Happy birthday to me!)) So Stay tuned, and maybe we&amp;#39;ll learn something together. I&amp;#39;m also going to cut out soda, and try to limit myself to coffee only (no syrups or real sugar), and cut out 95% of my candy. Sometimes, you just need chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;My Thoughts on the bottled soylent&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was going to go the premixed route, however browsing /r/soylent I saw a bunch of reports of mold in the bottles. So I&amp;#39;ll be avoiding it for now. It looks cool, but I&amp;#39;d rather not drink moldy soylent.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://zoeyrae.com/soylent/soylent-introduction/&quot;&gt;Soylent Introduction&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Zoey Cluff at &lt;a href=&quot;http://zoeyrae.com&quot;&gt;Zoey's World&lt;/a&gt; on November 16, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Idols]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://zoeyrae.com/life/idols/" />
  <id>http://zoeyrae.com/life/idols</id>
  <published>2015-11-13T01:39:42+00:00</published>
  <updated>2015-11-13T01:39:42+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Zoey Cluff</name>
    <uri>http://zoeyrae.com</uri>
    <email>zoey.cluff@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;No one&amp;#39;s ever really asked me who my idols are, and I&amp;#39;m always itching for it to happen for some reason. So why not post about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My biggest idol has to be Tyler Oakley. &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://zoeyrae.com/life/idols/&quot;&gt;Idols&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Zoey Cluff at &lt;a href=&quot;http://zoeyrae.com&quot;&gt;Zoey's World&lt;/a&gt; on November 13, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homelab]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://zoeyrae.com/play/homelab/" />
  <id>http://zoeyrae.com/play/homelab</id>
  <published>2015-11-11T09:18:32+00:00</published>
  <updated>2015-11-11T09:18:32+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Zoey Cluff</name>
    <uri>http://zoeyrae.com</uri>
    <email>zoey.cluff@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;I have a nifty little homelab setup that I use to tinker with to learn on. It&amp;#39;s nothing special, and it&amp;#39;s definately not &amp;quot;production&amp;quot; ready, but it&amp;#39;s fun to learn on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Base Specs&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CPU: AMD FX 8320&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memory: 20GB (soon to be 32GB) DDR3-1600&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GPU: AMD Radeon HD 7770 (Only GPU I had laying around that worked.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hard Drives: WD Green 2TB, WD Blue 1TB, WD Blue 500gb (Getting around to replacing them with matched drives soon)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS: VMWare ESXi 6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;What&amp;#39;s on it?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://zoeyrae.com/images/esxi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ESXI&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use the ESXi box for testing for work, along with things I want to play with that can&amp;#39;t be run locally. I&amp;#39;m in the process of spinning up new work VM&amp;#39;s for prototyping to implement redundancy, and some cool projects (like redis)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Windows VM&amp;#39;s:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two Active Directory Servers &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two DNS servers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WSUS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DHCP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Linux VM&amp;#39;s:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pfSense to act as a router to keep things separate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two DNS Servers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A gateway VM to work on VM&amp;#39;s that use the pfSense router so I can copy paste (something you can&amp;#39;t do from the ESXi console sadly)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Work Lab (Coming soon):&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two DNS servers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two Clustered MariaDB servers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two nginx machines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HAProxy load balancer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redis (on trial to see if it speeds anything up)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Puppet/Ansible (whatever one I pick)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logstash/Kibana/Elasticsearch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The work lab will eventually become production on Microsoft Azure (AWS I miss you!~). AWS is not my first pick, however Bizspark is quite nice and the Azure credits help. &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://zoeyrae.com/play/homelab/&quot;&gt;Homelab&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Zoey Cluff at &lt;a href=&quot;http://zoeyrae.com&quot;&gt;Zoey's World&lt;/a&gt; on November 11, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project Z Introduction]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://zoeyrae.com/project-z/project-x-introduction/" />
  <id>http://zoeyrae.com/project-z/project-x-introduction</id>
  <published>2015-11-11T02:52:32+00:00</published>
  <updated>2015-11-11T02:52:32+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Zoey Cluff</name>
    <uri>http://zoeyrae.com</uri>
    <email>zoey.cluff@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;Project Z is something unexpected. Why should we be be forced to have our privacy invaded in order to have some algorithm decide what ads to show us that oftentimes aren&amp;#39;t relevant? Practically any person with any basic tech knowledge knows what adblock is, and probably uses it to get rid of advertisements. Well, I&amp;#39;m out to change this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Introducing Project Z. The first advertising platform where YOU choose the ads. I along with many other people would stop using adblockers if the advertising were relevant to the things we&amp;#39;re interested in, and not having our privacy violated in the process. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project Z is simple, you log into the panel, and you see categories, you can assign each one a weight from 1-10 to get more relevant ads tailored to your browsing. That Amazon purchase you made that you wanted no one to know about suddenly filling up your ads showing the latest in kinky toys? No more! You can block that category, or any other for that matter and never see an ad like that again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Development is starting soon, follow @zoeyrcluff, and http://github.com/zoeycluff/ProjectX for updates!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://zoeyrae.com/project-z/project-x-introduction/&quot;&gt;Project Z Introduction&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Zoey Cluff at &lt;a href=&quot;http://zoeyrae.com&quot;&gt;Zoey's World&lt;/a&gt; on November 11, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>

</feed>
